

LUCAS NERI

DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Systems Development | Projects | Web Designer | Tests | Technologies | Support | Innovation | Systems |

I have experience working in the Technology area for 3 years and as a systems developer for 2 years

I have a multidisciplinary skill set that allows me to create solutions. I designed and developed web systems for thousands of people at EstrelaBet, Grupo SX and TicketClub.

I'm familiar to writing code in Vue, React, Javascript, Typescript, NodeJS, Golang, NextJS, JSX, and Python. I also use Docker, Swagger, JiraSoftware, MongoDB, MYSQL, AWS, EC2, GooglePlay, Linux (Terminal) among others tools. My interests are, Web Systems, Development and Systems Analyst, because are the functions I performed during mt career

https://lucasneri.com https://github.com/lucasneri

SKILLS AND COMPETENCES

- JavaScript, Typescript (Vue, React, Node, Next)
- Golang
- MYSQL, MONGO
- Python

CONTACT

Phone: +55 (31) 99230-3146 contato@lucasneri.com lucasneri.com

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Estrela Bet

Frontend Developer (may 2022 - present moment)

Analyze and develop systems projects, gather requirements, map processes and perform data modeling, in order to study and implement systems according to business rules. Analyze the performance of deployed systems, solve technical problems and prepare manuals

Main functions

- Project support
- Creating new Application
- Remake and Remaster Applications

Languages and Tools

- JavaScript, Typescript, Golang,
- Vue, React, Node, Next
- MYSQL, MONGO

Agile Methodologies

- Scrum
- Kanban

Communication Tools

- Discord
- Slack

Grupo SX

Frontend Developer (sep 2021 - may 2022)

Analyze and develop systems projects, gather requirements, map processes and perform data modeling, in order to study and implement systems according to business rules. Analyze the performance of deployed systems, solve technical problems and prepare manuals

Main functions

- Project support
- Creating new Application
- Remake and Remaster Applications

Full Stack Developer (june 2021 - sep 2021)

Web Designer, Developer and DesignerActivities: fullstack sites development, systems, maintenance, bug fixes, feature creation, improvements.

Main functions

- Project support
- Remaster Applications

Languages and Tools

- JavaScript, Typescript, Golang,
- Vue, React, Node, Next
- MYSQL, MONGO

Agile Methodologies

- Scrum
- Kanban

Communication Tools

- Discord
- Slack

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Self-employed

Mathematics Private Tut (aug 2019 - jun 2021)

Establish and enforce rules for behavior and policies and procedures to maintain order among students, prepare materials for class activities and Modify the general education curriculum for special-needs students based upon a variety of instructional techniques.

Main functions

- Support Students
- Prepare materials for class

My Ticket Club

Full Stack Developer (mar 2018 - jan 2019)

Developer and DesignerActivities: fullstack sites development, systems, maintenance, bug fixes, feature creation, improvements.

Main functions

- Project support

Languages and Tools

- JavaScript, PHP
- Angular
- MYSQL, MONGO

Localiza Hertz

Call Center Agent (oct 2018 - feb 2019)

Serve customers who needed to rent vehicles and reserve the vehicle for them

Main functions

- Reserve Vehicles

Sagendra

Trainee (aug 2015 - july 2016)

Study electronic and mechanical solutions by SENAI and help to repair some equipment

Main functions

- Repair electronic equipments

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

UFMG - Federal University in Minas Gerais

Bachelor's in Mathematics

SENAI

Electronics Technician

CTPMMG - Militar School

High school

UPTIME

English School

PROJECT

Cryptography

Scientific research (july 2020- dec 2020)

Studies on the complexity, security, difficulties and effectiveness of cryptographic systems directed by Lucas Reis, PhD in Mathematics (UFMG)

Main functions

- Research and tests on prime numbers
- Algorithm development

CERTIFICATES

Udemy

Javascript and Typescript Vue Golang

Rocketseat

React and React Native front-end (advanced)